mobiletor.com 2011-11-01

# Privacy

The terms ‘Mobiletor.com’ and ‘www.Mobiletor.com’ are used in this document (or Agreement) to refer to the Web site itself. Privacy issues are a high priority for us at www.Mobiletor.com and we follow standard industry practices to maintain your personal information. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. 

Mobiletor.com does not spam or sell/lease its user information to third parties. 

**Policy Coverage**

This Privacy Policy covers Mobiletor.com’s treatment of personally identifiable information that Mobiletor.com collects when you are on the www.Mobiletor.com site, and when you use Mobiletor.com’s services. This policy also covers Mobiletor.com’s treatment of any personally identifiable information that Mobiletor.com’s business partners share with Mobiletor.com. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Mobiletor.com does not own or control, or to people that Mobiletor.com does not employ or manage.  
Personal Information Collected by Mobiletor.com 

**ONLINE REGISTRATION** : In order to become a Mobiletor.com member, you must first create a member account on Mobiletor.com by providing information about yourself including but not limited to name, email address, country, ZIP/postal code, birth date, a brief summary of yourself and a password. Mobiletor.com checks for the validity of the email addresses. 

**OPTIONAL PROFILE INFORMATION** : Once you provide the basic information to create an account, you will have the opportunity to provide additional information in the Profile section describing your skills, interests, professional and academic background and favorites. Provision of this additional information beyond what is required at registration is entirely optional; it allows you to better identify yourself and create superior networking opportunities with others through shared contexts. but enables you to better identify yourself and find new opportunities on Mobiletor.com. Your Profile information can only be viewed by other Mobiletor.com visitors or registered members or members of your personal network only depending on the option you choose. 

**RECOGNIZING YOU AS A Mobiletor.com MEMBER** : For Mobiletor.com to recognize you as a registered member, you must login with your login email and password. At the time of login, you will have the option to instruct the site to remember you so when you come back the next time to use Mobiletor.com, you would not have to login with your email and password. As is common in the industry, Mobiletor.com uses the technology of cookies and site log files to monitor user registration, to recognize registered members when they revisit the site and to track site usage. Our ability to identify you as a registered member allows us to customize the Mobiletor.com experience and to protect your personal information based on your account settings. 

**INTERNET COMMUNICATION PROTOCOL INFORMATION** : The communication standards of the Internet industry transmit the URL of the site from which you visit www.Mobiletor.com, the IP address of your computer, the IP address of your ISP, various attributes of your computer such as operating system, resolution and browser software, and the date and time of your various requests for pages on www.Mobiletor.com. Mobiletor.com file logging system automatically logs all of this information in its log files for its analysis. 

**NEWSLETTER SUBSCRIPTIONS** : Visitors to Mobiletor.com may also sign up with their name and email address for a variety of newsletters that Mobiletor.com produces with varying frequency (e.g., News headlines) without having to register. Mobiletor.com confirms the subscription by sending an email to the email address specified before sending the newsletter. 

**USE OF INFORMATION BY Mobiletor.com**

Mobiletor.com is an online website that offers a variety of services designed to connect people from around the world. The information, whether personal information of any form of self-expression is used to help you describe yourself to other users. Mobiletor.com also collects additional information in order to operate and improve our service. www.Mobiletor.com is the sole owner of the information collected on the Mobiletor.com site. 

**VISIBILITY OF PUBLIC CREATIVE CONTRIBUTIONS** : In addition to being a social and professional networking site, Mobiletor.com also provides a variety of forums for its members to express themselves in the form of articles, columns, opinions, comments, reviews, art and photographs. Since this expression is linked to the member’s identity and the expression is in the public domain, the compilation of a member’s creative contributions to Mobiletor.com will be visible to all visitors of Mobiletor.com whether or not they are registered members of Mobiletor.com. 

**VISIBILITY OF PRIVATE MESSAGES WITHIN NETWORK** : You will be able to create and share messages within your personal network. The visibility of these private notes will be restricted to your network unless you or one of the members in your network chooses to forward it to others within or outside www.Mobiletor.com. 

**SHARING OF INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES** : Mobiletor.com takes your privacy very seriously. Mobiletor.com will never sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personally identifiable information to any third parties unless it is to carry out your instructions and to provide specific services. As an example, we send your information to a credit card processing company to process a payment you have made for the use of a Mobiletor.com service. These third parties are bound by strict confidentiality agreements which limit their use of such information. In addition, Mobiletor.com may share your information to send direct mailers or complimentary coupons/offers to a mailing agency to process postal mailing. Again, such an agency would be bound by strict confidentiality agreements that limit their use of such information. 

**EMAIL COMMUNICATIONS** : Mobiletor.com generally communicates with you as a registered member of Mobiletor.com through the primary email that you have specified at the time of registration. This is also used as the login text string in conjunction with the password to authenticate you on the www.Mobiletor.com site. Your email and password are never shared with anybody within or outside Mobiletor.com. Mobiletor.com uses this email address to send you three types of communications: 

Sending you emails related to the proper functioning of your account (e.g. when you receive a response to a classified you have posted on Mobiletor.com or when you receive an invitation to join the personal network of another person). Sending you newsletters that you have subscribed to. Sending you occasional announcements about changes in Mobiletor.com’s policies or promotions introduction of new services. Please note that these email communications may contain commercial messages of advertisers; however, Mobiletor.com does not provide your personal information or emails to any of the advertisers; we just include the advertising banners they provide us in the emails that we send. As always you can opt out of the newsletters or promotional announcements. 

**PARTNERING WITH OTHERS** : Mobiletor.com may partner with other online services to offer a combined service. Whenever we offer such combined services, Mobiletor.com will make it clear who the partner is and it will be entirely up to you to use or not to use the service. Where any personal information is passed along to the partner you will be informed prior to that sharing. 

**PROVISION OF AGGREGATE DEMOGRAPHIC INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES** : Mobiletor.com reserves the right to provide aggregate demographic information of its member base to advertisers and others so as to attract pertinent advertisers to advertise on Mobiletor.com. We do not shared personal information of individual users with advertisers. 

**COMMUNICATIONS TO OTHERS FROM YOU THROUGH Mobiletor.com** : You will be able to send emails to others — members and non-members — through the Mobiletor.com system. For example, you may send a comment on an article written by another member. Or you may send an email invitation to a non-member to join your personal network. In these instances, these emails will list your name and email address in the header of the message. The recipients of these emails initiated by you will get to know your name and email address. Mobiletor.com is not responsible for how these recipients use this information. Your contact information will only be shared with another member only if both of you indicated you would like to establish contact with each other. 

**COMMUNICATIONS FROM OTHERS TO YOU THROUGH Mobiletor.com** : Only registered members of Mobiletor.com are allowed to communicate with you through Mobiletor.com through a form on Mobiletor.com. Unless and until you respond to this email, they will not get to know your email address. You may, however, choose an account setting that prevents any other member from contacting you or inviting you to join their personal network. 

**DISCLOSURES REQUIRED BY LAW** : It is possible that we may need to disclose personal information when required by law. We will disclose such information wherein we have a good-faith belief that it is necessary to comply with a court order, ongoing judicial proceeding, or other legal process served on our company or to exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

**Third-party Advertising:** We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org.

We partner with ValueClick to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. ValueClick may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you. To learn more about this “behavioral advertising” practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, you can visit http://www.valueclickmedia.com/member_privacy.shtml
